BARON Z

• T: 0424790118

• Email: falconhui8@gmail.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A Front-end developer with one-year project experience in different aspects of web development including Page design, database and deployment.

I am seeking a position where I can apply my Problem-Solving skills and cooperate with teams to challenges.

Languages and Technologies

Languages JavaScript, HTML, CSS, XML

Frameworks React

Systems Linux, Windows

Skills Git control, SQL, Google Cloud, Photoshop, WordPress

Experience

Personal Resume development

May 2020- Aug 2020

This is a **ReactJS** based resume website. Data is fed directly from a **JSON file** which can be dynamically changed and showed on the website. The website is served by **Google Cloud**.

- The UI design.
- Designed the functions for the whole website.
- Fetched data from JSON file.
- Responsive functions such as email submission.
- Deployed through Google cloud.

URL: https://clever-hangar-282201.df.r.appspot.com

Git: git@github.com:Baronno/resume.git

Front-end development

Hospital management website

Aug 2018 - Oct 2018

- Created features, functionality and capabilities on websites using JavaScript, Ajax and JSON
- Collaborated with back-end developer to design API.
- Built the stable and maintainable codebases using React.
- Used **Bootstrap** to design the responsive web.
- Built the databases by mangodb which is a document database.
- Designed the layout by HTML and CSS.
- The efficiency increased around 60% after testing.

Front-end development Interactive Emergency Information System Aug 2018 – Oct 2018

- Collaborated with back end by Mean stack to develop the whole system.
- Analyzed customer's requirements by **Case diagram** and **Sequence diagram**.
- Designed the layout and content by HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Applied case diagram and sequence diagram to design the whole system.
- High Distinction.

Front End developer

Xingkaili company, Nanchang

Oct 2016 - Jan 2017

- Collaborated with the team member to finish the website of the enterprise.
- Used the **photoshop** to design the logo and designed the layout by **HTML** and **CSS**.
- Used **React** and written in JavaScript to develop the front end.
- Worked with the back-end team efficiently to design API.
- Deployed **Node.js** to connect with the server.
- Did the **usability test** by update the comment function to collect the customer feedback.
- This website finally Increased 20% percent of the sales.
- This project reduced **60%** commuting time.

EDUCATION

Master of software system Engineer

July 2017 - Jun 2019

University of Technology Sydney

Courses with Distinction:

- Engineering Graduate Project.
- Database Principle.
- Cloud Computing and Software as a service.
- Web technology.
- Leadership and responsibility.
- Fundamentals of Software Development.

Bachelor of Electronic engineering

Sep 2012- Jun 2016

Heilongjiang University

Key area: Semiconductor, Single-Chip Microcomputer and C programming.